xappie.com 2019-03-31

# Xappie

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected by Nevexa Digital Private Limited. d/b/a www.xappie.com, (“Xappie”, “us”, “we” “our”), how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. By using the website http://www.xappie.com (the “Site”) and the services, features, content, applications or widgets, as well as mobile device applications offered by Xappie (collectively with the Site, the “Services”), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy forms an integral part of Xappie’s Terms of Service, which is incorporated by reference. Any capitalized term used but not defined in this Policy will have the meaning defined in the Terms of Use. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the Services.

**The Information Xappie May Collect**

## 1\. Information You Provide

Xappie may collect and store any personal information you enter through the Services or the Site. This may include personally identifying information, such as your name, username, residence, e-mail address, birthdate, pictures, and/or credit card information. Xappie may also request information about your interests and activities, and location. No system can be completely secure. Therefore, Xappie does not promise, and you should not expect, that such information may not be inadvertently collected and that such personal information will remain secure. 

You also may give us permission to access your information on other services. If you connect to the Services using your Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram or other third-party service credentials (each, a “Supported Platform”), you authorize us to collect your authentication information, such as your username, encrypted access credentials, and other information that may be available on or through your Supported Platform account, including but not limited to your name, pictures, and friends/followers lists. The information we get from Supported Platforms may depend on your settings or their privacy policies. 

Xappie does not store any user financial information, even though we may request information about you and your credit card and/or bank account. Xappie does not store certain financial data due to its use of third party agents, such as PayPal, as its financial transaction facilitator. Please refer to such third parties' Terms (https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/useragreement-full) and Privacy Policies (https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) for more information about how these parties use your information. We do not store any user financial information, even though we may request information about yourself and your credit card and/or bank account. That financial information is handled, processed, and stored by the third party financial transaction processing companies. To the extent that Xappie uses third party providers such as PayPal for financial transaction services, we believe that such third parties take the privacy of your personal information seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of their privacy policies. 

## 2\. Information Collected Automatically

Like many sites on the Internet, the Site automatically collects information from your browser when you visit the Site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from Xappie (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. If you use Xappie's mobile application, Xappie may collect various non-identifying information, such as your mobile device type, device properties, IP address, profile views, ad views, ad clicks, search queries, store and product views, photo views, and page views. We may also combine all of this non-identifying information with other non-identifying information to infer interests or demographic characteristics. In order for Xappie to work with your iPhone, iPod touch, iPad, BlackBerry, or other mobile device, Xappie must collect your Device Identification Code or "DIC". The DIC is a special type of identifier used in software applications in order to provide a unique reference number for applications like those used by your mobile device. Your DIC is not shared with other users. 

## 3\. Cookies and Use of Cookie Data

Like many sites on the Internet, when you visit the Site, Xappie may assign your computer one or more cookies to facilitate access to the Site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, Xappie also may automatically collect information about your online activity on the Site, such as the web pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on the Site. Xappie may use this data to better understand how you interact with the Site, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Services. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able use some of the interactive features offered on the Site. In addition, please be aware that other parties may also place their own cookies on or through the Site, and may collect or solicit personal information from you. Other cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to the registration data you have submitted to Xappie in hashed, non-human readable form. No personally identifiable information is contained in these cookies.

If you use Xappie's mobile device applications, Xappie may also use mobile cookies. A mobile cookie is a small data file transferred to your mobile device for record-keeping purposes. These mobile cookies help Xappie track session-based information and also better understand the effectiveness of the Services (by way of example only, by keeping track of the location and context in which you view a user profile). These mobile cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

## 4\. Information Collected by Third Parties

Xappie may allow third parties, advertising companies, and ad networks to display advertisements on the Site and via the Services. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Xappie does not provide any personal information to these third parties. 

If you connect your Xappie account to a Supported Platform, the default setting is generally that Xappie automatically allows users to share users’ activity and activity-related stories with that Services. You understand that such information may be attributed to your account on Supported Platforms and may be published on such Services either directly by you or by other users. 

You understand and agree that Supported Platforms’ or other third parties’ use of information they collect from you is governed by their privacy policies, and Xappie’s use of such information is governed by this Privacy Policy.

## 5\. Agents

Xappie employs or engages other companies and individuals (including but not limited to PayPal) to perform business functions on behalf of the Site and Services. These persons are provided with personal identifying information required to perform their functions, but are prohibited by contract from using the information for other purposes. These persons engage in a variety of functions which include, but are not limited to, fulfilling orders, removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing user services. 

Any supplied billing information (if collected by and through the Site, as opposed to being directly inputted and collected by and through third parties such as PayPal) shall be encrypted for transmittal to a third-party intermediary for processing. Such billing information is used only to bill you for those purchases you choose to make through the Site. The process is designed to protect your billing information against unauthorized misappropriation by third parties. As the technological landscape is constantly changing, no security system is absolutely secure. Xappie cannot and does not guarantee the security of any of its databases and information contained therein, nor can Xappie guarantee any supplied information will be absolutely secure from interception during transmission to the Site over the Internet.

**How Xappie Uses the Information It Collects**  
Xappie may use information that it collects as described above to:  
\- provide you with customer support  
\- deliver the services that you have requested  
\- enforce or exercise any rights in Xappie’s Terms of Use.  
\- perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

Xappie may also release your personal information to a third-party in order to protect, establish, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; comply with a subpoena, court order, legal process, or other legal requirement; or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, threats to our property, or as necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. 

Through your settings within the Site and Services, you can choose which communications you receive from us, manage your public profile information, and set your sharing preferences. To change, customize, or limit access to or sharing of information collected from Supported Platforms, please visit your account settings on the Site or Services.

**Listing and Transaction Information**  
Please note that to the extent you include any personal information in any content you upload to the Service, we have the right to publish that content in connection with the operation of the Service. 

As part of the buying and selling process, Xappie will facilitate the sharing of the buyer’s shipping address and other information with the seller. As part of the buying and selling process, sellers may obtain a buyer’s email address, shipping address, payment information, and/or other information. Sellers may use this information only for Xappie-related communications or for Xappie-facilitated transactions. Xappie has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages or unauthorized transactions. Without express consent from that person, you must not add any Xappie member to your email or physical mailing list or store or misuse any information.

**Public Spaces**  
Xappie is both a marketplace and a community. We offer several features that allow members to connect and communicate in public or semi-public spaces. Please use common sense and good judgment when posting in these community spaces or sharing your personal information with other users on Xappie. Be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others, or could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Xappie generally does not remove content from community spaces, and your posts may remain public after your account is closed. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to post in community spaces on Xappie, including but not limited to store and product reviews.

**Third-Party Websites**  
There are a number of places on the Site and the Services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on the Site or the Services, you may be taken to a website that Xappie does not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you. Xappie recommends that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting. 

**Advertising and spamming:**  
Commercial messages or promotional messages from businesses or Organizations are not permitted on the network. Xappie provides a Platform for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photos but the website must not be used as a medium for marketing or selling to our members.

No advertising or promotion is allowed except where it is for an event, Classified, publication or similar item that has direct relevance to the subject of discussion and is non-commercial in nature. Information about locating and sharing knowledge and expertise is welcomed, but must have relevance to the topic on which an opinion is expressed or a discussion is initiated.

Do not recruit members to join another website forum or chat group, whether personal or otherwise. if you have a suggestion for a new forum, please contact us or send your queries to forums@xappie.com. Do not post chain letters, promote pyramid schemes or recruit members for any network marketing or multilevel marketing businesses.

Xappie encourages healthy discussion on the topics that members contribute to in forums and where relevant, members are allowed to post links to their content. However, overt promotion of, or inappropriate links to other known commercial websites on any forum are not permitted and will be removed. If you are unsure whether a link or a posting is allowed, please send your queries to forums@xappie.com. The definition of an appropriate link is one that is relevant to both the posting and the forum topic. A commercial site is considered as one which promotes a product or service for a price or for other consideration that suggests it is a for-profit business.

**Copyrighted material**  
Uploading copies of copyrighted material as a whole or in part on Xappie without explicit permission from the copyright owner shall be deemed to infringe on the copyright and this applies to materials such as text, images, music, movies, games, and other software in digital and analog format. Xappie reserves the right to immediately delete such material without prior permission / consultation from the member. If you suspect that an image submitted to Xappie.com is copyright protected and has been used fraudulently, please contact us immediately or send us an email to support@xappie.com.

**Safety guidelines**  
The Platform is always reaching out to a wider audience by showcasing the best of our member contributions. However, in doing so, we will not allow to be uploaded anything on the site that we think could be potentially endangering or is inflammatory or embarrassing to our members. It also helps members to be aware of certain things in the interest of their safety.

All members are responsible for the safety of their personal information. We recommend that members use their discretion to disclose their names, addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers or other personal information online. Xappie cannot be held liable for any misuse of this information in anyways. If you are worried about someone else using this information to cause any kind of issues or damages then please do not submit them.

All members need to be aware that when they upload their photos on the Platform, the photos are not only visible to the entire internet community but can also be downloaded, since any image that can be displayed on a computer screen can be saved by the person viewing it. It is technically not possible to prevent this and hence Xappie cannot be held liable in such cases. If you are worried about someone else viewing or saving your images then please do not submit them.

**Google Analytics**  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help analyze the usage of the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States in most cases.

In case IP-anonymization is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and then truncated there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP address, that your browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en

**Google AdSense or AdMob**  
This website uses Google AdSense or Google AdMob, a service for including advertisements from Google Inc. ("Google"). Google AdSense uses "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer, to analyze the use of this website. Google AdSense uses also use web beacons (invisible graphics). Through these web beacons information such as traffic can be analyzed.

This usage information, generated by cookies and web beacons (including your IP address) and the display of advertisements are transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. This information can be given to Google partners. But Google will not associate your IP-address with other saved data they have from you. You can prevent the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, we point out that in this case you may not be able to fully use all features of this website. By using this website you agree to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described above and for the aforementioned purpose.

**Twitter**  
Our website contains plugins from Twitter. These plugins are solely provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. Through the use of Twitter and the "Re-tweet" function, the web pages you visit will be linked to your Twitter account and be visible to other users. Data will also be transferred to Twitter. We point out that we as providers of the site have no knowledge of the content of the transmitted data and its use by Twitter. For more information, please see the privacy policy of Twitter at <https://twitter.com/privacy>. You can change your privacy preferences at Twitter in the account settings.

**Use of Facebook Social Plugins**  
Our website uses plugins provided by the social network facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo or the "Lik button. For a full list of Facebook plugins please see: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of our website with your IP address. If you click the FB "Like" button while you are logged in on Facebook, the content of our page can be linked on your Facebook profile. Therefore if you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. We point out that we do not have knowledge about the data gathered and its use by Facebook. For more information, please visit Facebook's privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your Facebook member data, please log off Facebook before entering our website.

**Children's Privacy**  
Xappie forbids the use of the Site and Services to individuals age 18 and below, without the consent of a parent or guardian over the age of 18. Xappie does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
Xappie will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When Xappie posts changes to this Privacy Policy, it will revise the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Xappie recommends that you check the Site from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of Xappie’ s other policies. 

**Responsible authority**  
Questions regarding data privacy and protection should be addressed to [privacy@xappie.com](mailto:privacy@xappie.com)
